Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Kowski. On this podcast, I show
you how to grow your business, how to
make more money as a coach, mentor,
trainer, or consultant. And I want to
show you today a topic that is going to
help you tremendously as you're
marketing your business, as you're
building it. It's a habit that you need
to develop more than anything else.
There's a book that I've been reading
and I've been developing over the last
couple of months my skills at trading
stocks. In fact, over the last month or
so, I've generated over $40,000 in
profit just trading stocks. And it's
incredible because this is a skill that
I've been wanting to learn for a long
time. But it comes off the the the
balance of back in June, um, I made a a
decision when trading, I traded an
options trade and I lost $12,000 in
almost an instant by doing this within
the same day. And it was just, it felt
devastating. It felt really hard. It
felt really difficult. I since crawled
myself out of that. I gained far more
than I had lost. And I learned a habit
of resilience that I think it goes far
beyond just trading stocks, but it also
applies in building your business. And
it's something that I've developed in
building businesses over the last 23
years. It's something that my mentors
have taught me. And it's something that
I've seen has the most tremendous impact
on your life as a business owner and
your ability to be resilient.
And what it is is the ability to move
quickly past mistakes that you make.
This is a concept that I find that a lot
of people fight because they sit in the
feelings of a mistake for far too long.
I've seen clients actually sit in a
mistake for over 12 to 24 months for one
mistake that they made. And this is
actually an indicator of where they're
at mentally. And it's a skill and an
ability that needs to be grown.
You see, when you're running a marketing
campaign, when you're scaling your
business, when you're trying to grow
your business, you're trying to get
clients, you are going to inevitably
inevitably make mistakes that may not
turn out how you want them to initially.
You might get the pixel wrong on your
site. you might um you know just not get
anybody who opts into your campaign. And
these are things that when we go into
it, we need to make sure of that we
understand are part of the process.
Realize that every time that we run a
campaign, it can either win or it'll
lose. And instead of seeing things as
losers, see them as potentials for
learning. any mistake that you make, no
longer seeing it as a mistake. And
that's what this book actually teaches.
It actually teaches that to actually
develop the ability in trading stocks,
you need to not see your mistakes as
mistakes, but rather as data to learn
from and to then move forward and to
take action on even the same thing. You
see, especially when it comes to trading
stocks, but I believe it also applies to
business.
You're going to touch a few hot stoves
and you're going to have to literally go
back and touch the hot stove again. But
realize that you have a glove on and you
have the ability to do so with wisdom
and knowledge. And this is one of the
biggest things that stops people because
we know that internally our brain is
wired to not touch a hot stove.
We are wired to not do the thing
that hurt us.
Let's say you ran a campaign and it
didn't produce the results that you
wanted or you made a mistake on
something.
The skill to develop is the ability to
literally go back and do that thing
again, but with new data, with
adjustments,
with a few rules in mind. I'm going to
check on my pixel. I'm going to get some
help to help me build my campaign out
better. I'm not going to let this one
situation stop me from going back. See,
you wouldn't do that in your
relationships. I mean, maybe you would.
I guess some relationships, if they're a
toxic relationship, you might get out of
them, but there are other relationships
that you would not do them in. Say your
marriage or things like that, and you
might approach it with different data
and a different approach. And so in your
business, I suggest not to treat it like
a toxic relationship, though it may feel
like it sometimes. It might feel like
the most toxic relationship that you're
in. Rather,
see it as, okay, what can I learn from
this? And how can I quickly quickly
learn from my mistakes,
get back on the horse again, keep moving
forward? You know, this past week,
remember I told you I had over $40,000
in gains in the last last month in
profit? Well, I had a day on Thursday,
and it was a day where I my mindset was
not in the right place, and just
everything was going wrong. And I lost
$3,000. This was this week.
And I had I and I had actually made that
$3,000 over the course of the the prior
week and a half. So, all of my gains for
the prior week and a half were wiped out
in one day of me uh they have the thing
it's called house money fallacy. I
learned this um because I was up so much
I was like well I can afford to lose it
but here's the truth really not really
that to grow my bis my business my
stocks my portfolio my family
you got to take money off the table and
you got to not see it as okay this is
house money so I can lose it and it's a
concept where you establish certain
rules of okay I'm not going to do this
I'm going to make sure to do this and
things like that I was able to be
resilient the next day. But I literally
I actually read this book. I listened to
the audio book of it. It's on YouTube.
You actually can't find the audio book
anywhere for the It's called The
Disciplined Trader by Mark Douglas. You
can't find the audio book anywhere, but
somebody scanned the book in and put
it's on YouTube. It's like 6 hours long.
It's incredible. It's one of the best
audio books. And I and what I was
thinking the whole time I was listening
to it is every concept in this book
translates to business for my business
owners.
You don't have to be trading stocks, but
it's a winning mental attitude of okay,
mistakes don't actually exist.
They are just data to learn from and
grow and to move forward. And listen,
that might like throw your mind for a
loop, but can I tell you that if you
start to look at mistakes that you make
as that is they're just data that I can
learn from, move forward, get back on,
and do it again,
your business will change because you
will have the consistency, the momentum,
and the ability. See, every time that
you make a mistake is still part of your
momentum because you actually did
something.
because you actually got
into action. You took action. You did
something. And that's more than most
people can say.
And so by developing the winning habit,
the winning mindset of okay, mistakes
are just data
I can learn from. And snowboarder Shawn
White actually talks about this in
snowboarding. The exact same concept. He
had a massive
injury in the Olympics if you remember
public stage,
smashed his head up
and uh he got back up got back got back
out there. He got back out there in the
Olympics rather and he says that he does
not see things as losing ever. He sees
it as either winning or learning.
I can either win or I can learn from
this.
but it doesn't mean that I'm going to
run from it. It doesn't mean that I'm
going to say it was a failure.
And that's a habit and that's the
winning mindset to have is that we don't
see things as failures. We actually are
looking to fail often. And this is
something that I I know I've developed
over the years is that I am looking to
have moments of failure because what
they do is they teach me where to grow.
They teach me what to do differently. I
do this in my marriage, in my
relationships with my family. Now, I'm
not working intentionally to fail, but
I'm looking to develop habits and
mindsets that keep me moving forward. I
had this failure in trading stocks this
weekend, this week. But the next day, I
was able to actually recover about $600
of that in profit. And listen, most
traders aren't able to get back up again
and do that again after a loss like
that. I know I wasn't in the past, but
it was the winning mindsets of this book
right here. And I'll I'll, you know,
I'll report back here in a week or so
where I'm at on this. I might even teach
some of the concepts what I've been
doing with trading
and doing a a really profitable scalping
strategy. Um, and so with that,
what I want to share with you is that
just learn
to
be okay with your mistakes. Love
yourself through them.
Say it's okay. It's all right.
And it's all right to to get right back
on it. Maybe not the same day, but the
next day.
that if you can learn this concept of
I'm going to learn it's going to be data
for learning you will transform your
life and business. All right listen if
you're a mentor coach or consultant
service provider who wants to grow your
business and make more money wealthy
coach academy program is the place to do
so where we show you exactly step by
step what to do. I come alongside you
personally and walk you through the
process in our community. I answer your
questions. We have courses in there that
literally will answer every question
that you have, walk you through every
process that's out there, but you also
get personal interaction with me in
there and it's an incredible experience.
My wealthy coach academy program will
change your life. Promise you that. Grow
your life everybody. We'll talk soon.
Have a good one.
[Music]
[Applause]